<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastian Suchanowski</title>
    <link>http://www.suchanowski.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sebastian Suchanowski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.suchanowski.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Buying a multipurpose camera - Panasonic DMC-LX15</title>
      <link>http://www.suchanowski.com/blog/buying-multipurpose-camera-panasonic-dmc-lx15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.suchanowski.com/blog/buying-multipurpose-camera-panasonic-dmc-lx15/</guid>
      <description>As I personally decided that year 2018 will be a year of content for me it was about time to finally buy my first camera. I have spent some time on the research and this might help you if you have similar needs as I.
Main criteria I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be photography or videography pro and because of that, I was looking for a compact camera which won&amp;rsquo;t require much more investments as I will learn to use it and will find the new and more fitting way of using it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Tech Talk 2011 - Berlin</title>
      <link>http://www.suchanowski.com/blog/apple-tech-talk-2011-berlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.suchanowski.com/blog/apple-tech-talk-2011-berlin/</guid>
      <description>As all iOS developers know tickets for this year conference were booked almost immediately. At first, I thought that the scale of the event will be much bigger (however doing it in 9 cities is not piece of cake – if it all will be as well organized as the one in Germany). I&amp;rsquo;ve counted about 350 seats in the room where the KickOff part took place – as usual, started with some statistics – which is very typical for Apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing the college admission essay</title>
      <link>http://www.suchanowski.com/blog/writing-the-college-admissions-essay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.suchanowski.com/blog/writing-the-college-admissions-essay/</guid>
      <description>Let me start with a little introduction. In 2010 I was about to graduate from the Military University of Technology in Warsaw (engineer degree - sort of bachelor degree but fancier) and I decided that I will apply to a few of ivy league schools - my grades were not outstanding, my English not perfect and financially it was impossible without scholarship but I thought, what the heck, I will try anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
